{
    "question": "Contoh soal expression of suggestioun? \u00a0",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "woman ; l think the weather is not friendly enough for us to do outdoor activites.<br>mam ; <br>narator ; what will the mam likely reply with?<br>a. enjoy your flight<br>b.let&#039;s go to the beach.<br>c. yes . we&#039;d better cancel our trip<br>d. l don&#039;t think l can attend the meeting<br><br>jawaban c<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "ubah-kalimat-tersebut-ke-dalam-bentuk-pasif-1-it-is-said-that-ma-237",
            "question": "Ubah kalimat tersebut ke dalam bentuk pasif    1. It is said that many people are homeless after floods\r\n2. People say that Arthur is very rich\r\n3. People say that he has 22 children\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. It is said that many people are homeless after floods<br>-- ini udah pasif ya?\u00a0<br>Many people are homeless due to flood, it is said by the newspaper<br><br>2. People say that Arthur is very rich<br>Arthur is very rich, is said by people<br><span><br>3. People say that he has 22 children\u00a0<br>he has 22 children, is said by people\u00a0<br><br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "22-milyar-dalam-mata-uang-dolar-senilai-dengan-210-663",
            "question": "2,2 milyar dalam mata uang dolar senilai dengan ?........\r\n$\u00a0210,000\r\natau 2,2 billion ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Billion = Milyar<br>Million = Juta<br>Tetapi, bila 2,2 milyar rupiah dibuat ke dalam dolar, maka sekitar $210,000. Karena dolar dengan rupiah kan lebih tinggi dolar...",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "yaitu, senilai dengan $210,000<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "boleh-minta-contoh-soal-dari-ungkapan-maksud-532",
            "question": "Boleh minta contoh soal dari ungkapan maksud?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Maksud -&gt; Idea or opinion<br><br>I think the best way to be expert in mathematics is by practicing everyday.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "di-suruh-mengubah-kalimat-berikut-ke-dalam-bentuk-pasif-mereka-so-444",
            "question": "Di suruh     mengubah kalimat berikut ke dalam bentuk pasif mereka\r\n\r\n soalnya\" it is dais that many people are homeless after floods\"\r\npeople say that arthur is very rich",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "it is dais were\u00a0nomeless after floods by many people dan People was say athur is very rich.<br><br>Sorry if im wrong ty:)x",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "combine-the-sentences-using-too-so-or-either-and-neither-1-d-745",
            "question": "Combine the sentences using : Too, so, or either and neither    1. Dogs\u00a0can't eat vegetables. Cats can't eat vegetables\r\n2. We haven't eaten yet. Father hasn't yet\r\n3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not seventeen years old\r\n\r\nJawabannya yang Jelas ya :)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. Dogs can&#039;t eat vegetables. Neither can cats<br>2. We haven&#039;t eaten yet. Father hasn&#039;t either<br>3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not either<br><br>setau aku begitu aja sih udah betul. mudah-mudahan membantu ya:)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-buatin-dialog-expresing-anger-untuk-2-orang-524",
            "question": "Tolong buatin dialog expresing anger :)\r\nuntuk 2 orang",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Everyone Has Bad Day<br>Sari\t: Hey, Rangga!<br> Rangga\t: What displeasure!<br> Sari\t: What? What happened, Rangga? Are you angry about something?<br> Rangga\t: Oh, I\u2019m very sorry, Sari. I was walking near handkerchief. You can wipe up your wet shirt.<br>Rangga\t: Oh, thank you, Sari. So, how was your day, Sari? Did something bad happen to you too? Haha I\u2019m kidding, Sari.<br> Sari\t: Actually, something bad did happen to me. It\u2019s still driving me mad until now.<br> Rangga\t: Oh, really? What do you look so insulted about?<br>\n Sari\t: It\u2019s my boss. He said that I can have a day-offs earlier but \ntoday he revoked what he said. I was planning on going for a vacation on\n my day-offs with my family. I am extremely displeased about that.<br> Rangga\t: I\u2019m sorry to hear that.<br> Sari\t: Well, everyone has bad day but if we still consider it positively, everything is going to be alright<br> Rangga\t: Yeah, I think you\u2019re right<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "A = <span>why are you scared?<br>B = i&#039;am sorry. i spoil your diary.<br>A = what?? why did you do that?<br>B = i didn&#039;t purposely. sorry<br>A = wether the sorry can repair all?<br>B = OK. i will replace your diary, but iam sorry<br>A = it&#039;s up to you. <br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-describe-dengan-tema-my-beloved-home-386",
            "question": "Tolong describe dengan tema \"my beloved home\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "My beloved home<br><br>It is located in the central park. My home is the sweetest home on my complex. It has green roof which is made from special clay. Therefore it is always shining when the sun light rise in the morning.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "my home.. my everything.. even\u00a0my home not as huge the president home or a museums.. even my home don&#039;t as rich as the businessman home.. i love my home.. because my home protect me from the light of the sun , from the extreme weather , from the cold of the rain.. but i still love my home..home sweet home.. you&#039;re my protecter from childhood.. how bad you&#039;re you still my home... i called it my beloved home",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "choose-inappropriate-structure-in-the-following-sentences-or-dial-968",
            "question": "choose inappropriate structure in the following sentences or dialog below ! man : how's your new job at the hospital ? \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 A woman : it's great and my co-workers sre so nice \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 B \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 C man : good. that's important for you to feel exciting with your workers \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0D",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>man : good. that&#039;s important for you to feel <u>exciting</u> with your workers</span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-yang-membuatmu-suka-dengan-cerita-malin-kundang-apa-saja-yg-d-727",
            "question": "Apa yang membuatmu suka dengan cerita malin kundang    apa saja yg dapat diambil (pelajaran) dari cerita tersebut?? (minimal 2)\r\n\r\njawabnya pakai bahasa inggris y.. \r\nplease....",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "tidak boleh membantah kedua orang tua ..<br>maaf gk bisa bhs. inggris !!<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "1. bercerita realiti dan fakta<br>2. bisa dijadikan pelajaran buat kita<br><br>hikmhanx kita tidak boleh melawan ortu terutama ibu kita,, karena dia yg mengandung kita selama 9 bulan",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-perbedaan-antara-simple-past-tense-dengan-present-perfect-ten-100",
            "question": "Apa perbedaan antara simple past tense dengan present perfect tense ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Simple pastanse untuk menyatakan kejadian yang sudah lalu<br>present perfect untuk menyatakan kejadian yang direncanakan",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "simple past tense dipakai saat keterangan waktunya sudah selesai, \nsedangkan present perfect dipakai saat keterangan waktunya belum \nselesai/masih berlanjut.<br>Contoh:<br>I bought 3 books last week. (simple past-last week sudah berlalu)<br>I have bought 3 books this week. (present perfect-this week belum berlalu, masih berlangsung)<br><br>present perfect menggunakan &#039;for&#039; dan &#039;since&#039; saat kegiatannya masih berlanjut.<br><br>I have lived in London for 3 years. (present perfect-masih berlangsung, sekarang pun masih di London)<br>I have lived in London since 1990. (sampai sekarang masih tinggal di London)\n<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}